Guide to the Consumer Reports. Consumer-Farmer Milk Cooperative records, 1904-1988 and undated RL.11793
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Organizations, 1904-1977 and undated; 5
  - Housing Associations, 1933-1970; 6
    - Matthew Napear, 1934-1954 (Box 13)
      Matthew Napear (1894-1968) served as Secretary of the New York City Department of Sanitation and as the New York Chairman of the Consolidated Home and Farm Owners Mortgage Committee
    - Matthew Napear--Consolidated Home and Farm Owners Mortgage Committee, 1933-1940 (Box 13)
    - Meadow Lake Estates--Utopia Park Villas at Flushing lot map, 1934 (Oversize-folder 1)
    - National Communities Corporation, 1938 (Box 13)
    - National Public Housing Conference, 1938-1946 (Box 13)
    - New York City Housing Authority, 1948-1956 (Box 13)
    - Pamphlets, flyers, etc., 1934-1962 (Box 13)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, 1936-1970; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - United States Federal Housing Administration, 1935 (Box 14)
    - United States Housing Authority, 1938-1940 (Box 14)
  - International Organizations, 1919-1943 and undated; 7
    - Canada--James McFadyen: The Cooperative Movement and Post-War Reconstruction, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Finland, 1931-1936 (Box 14)
    - General--Co-Operative Information Bulletin, undated (Box 14)
    - Great Britain, 1919-1935 (Box 14)
    - Great Britain--London Cooperative Society Ltd. Placard, 1946 (Box 19)
    - Sweden (in English, German, Swedish), 1931-1937; 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Producer Organizations, 1936-1970; 8
    - Borden's, Sheffield Farms, 1937-1942 (Box 14)
    - Chateaugay Cooperative Marketing Association, 1938-1947 (Box 14)
    - Dairy Farmers Union, 1939-1942 (Box 14)
    - Dairy Farmers Union--Correspondence, 1939-1941; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Dairy Farmers Union--Journal, reports, etc., 1936-1970 (Box 14)
    - Dairy Farmers Union--Open letters, financial reports, etc., 1939-1942 (Box 14)
    - Dairy Farmers Union--Parodneck v. Dairy Farmers Union, 1941; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Dairymen's League, 1935-1962 (Box 14)
    - Delaware County Farmers Cooperative, 1940-1943 (Box 14)
    - Delaware Valley Farmers Cooperative Association, 1937-1941 (Box 14)
    - Delaware Valley Feed Cooperative, 1943 (Box 14)
    - Eastern Farm Products, 1942-1955 (Box 14)
    - Farmers Union Dairy Cooperative--Frenchtown, New Jersey, 1941-1952 (Box 14)
    - Farmers Union Dairy Cooperative--Greencastle, Pennsylvania, 1939-1946 (Box 14)
    - Farmers Union Dairy Cooperative--Tuckerton, Pennsylvania, 1943-1970; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Farmers Union Federation of Cooperatives, 1945-1963 (Box 14)
    - Farmers Union of the New York Milkshed, 1941-1960; 3 folders (Box 15)
    - FLF Farmers Union Cooperative Association, 1945-1949 (Box 15)
    - Fly Creek Valley Cooperative Association, 1938-1951; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Fly Creek Valley Cooperative Association--Photographs, 1940s; 2 folders (Box 18)
      Includes photographs of bonfire, events
    - General, 1947-1955 (Box 15)
    - Hillside Producers Cooperative, 1938-1945 (Box 15)
    - International Federation of Agricultural Producers, 1947 (Box 15)
    - Lisle Producers Cooperative, 1941-1945 (Box 15)
    - National Dairy Products Corporaton, 1937-1940 (Box 15)
    - National Farmers Union/Farmers Educational and Cooperative Union, 1946-1952; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - National Farmers Union/Farmers Educational and Cooperative Union--Eastern Division, 1945-1958; 3 folders (Box 15)
    - National Farmers Union/Farmers Educational and Cooperative Union--Northeastern Division, 1944-1951 (Box 15)
    - National Farmers Union/Farmers Educational and Cooperative Union--Printed materials, 1942-1955 (Box 15)
    - National Farmers Union/Farmers Educational and Cooperative Union--Songbooks, 1944-1947 (Box 15)
      Includes: Favorite Songs of the Farmers Union; Singing Farmers
    - National Farmers Union/Farmers Educational and Cooperative Union--Wright v. Farm Journal and Farmer's Wife, 1944-1951; 2 folders (Box 15)
      Archie Wright, head of Farmers Union, defamation suit against a Farm Journal article accusing Wright of Communist influence
    - National Farmers Union Education Service, 1947 (Box 15)
    - New Jersey--General, 1943-1945 (Box 15)
    - New Jersey Federated Egg Producers Cooperative Association, 1946-1950 (Box 15)
    - Sheffield Farms, 1945 (Box 15)
    - Stage Door Canteen, 1943 (Box 18)
      Photographs of milk served during lunch for military personnel during World War II
    - Sullivan County Dairy Cooperative, 1943-1954 (Box 15)
    - Wampsville Dairymen's Corporation, 1942-1943 (Box 15)
    - Worcester Cooperative Association, 1938 (Box 15)
    - York County Cooperative, 1945-1957 (Box 16)
  - Other Organizations, 1936-1950; 9
    - Alphabetical file A-Z (in English, Hebrew), 1936-1948 (Box 16)
    - National Lawyers Guild, 1939-1949 (Box 16)
    - National Nutrition Conference for Defense, 1941 (Box 16)
    - National Religion and Labor Foundation, 1947-1950 (Box 16)
    - New York County Lawyers Association, 1937-1941 (Box 16)
    - Progressive Citizens of America, 1947-1948 (Box 16)
    - Progressive Party/Henry Wallace, 1948-1949 (Box 16)
    - Society for the Prevention of World War III, 1947-1949; 3 folders (Box 16)
      Includes: Prevent World War III magazine issues
  - Rutland Railroad, 1904-1963; 10
    - Correspondence, 1946-1963; 3 folders (Box 16)
      Files document efforts by CFMC to acquire and reorganize the railroad as a cooperative.
    - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1946-1950; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Legal, 1904-1951 (Box 16)
    - Newspaper articles, 1946-1951 (Box 16)
- Printed Material, 1933-1978 and undated; 6
  - Amalgamated Housing--A.H. Co-Op Community News, 1945 Dec. (Box 16)
  - Bill Davidson--Milk 12c a Quart: Why Not In Your Town (Collier's), 1955 Apr. 29 (Box 19)
  - Borden--The Borden Eagle, 1934 May (Box 19)
  - Business Week, 1938 Apr. 23 (Box 16)
  - C.J. Blanford--The Market Administrator's Bulletin, 1943 (Box 16)
  - Central Jersey Farmers Cooperative Association--Central Jersey Farmers Cooperative Voice, 1943 May (Box 19)
  - Chicago Co-Op Congress News, 1940 (Box 16)
  - Common Council for American Unity--Legislative News Letter, 1940 Aug. 19 (Box 16)
  - Common Sense, 1934, 1943 (Box 16)
  - Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO)--Economic Outlook, 1945-1953 (Box 16)
  - Consumer-Farmer Milk Cooperative--Consumer-Farmer Cooperator, 1946-1978; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Consumer-Farmer Milk Cooperative--Reprints, posters, etc., 1940-1970 (Box 19)
  - Consumer-Farmer Milk Cooperative--The Link, 1939-1941 (Box 16)
  - Consumer-Farmer Milk Cooperative--The Organized Consumer, 1941-1945 (Box 16)
  - Consumer-Farmer Milk Cooperative--The Organized Consumer, 1938-1940; 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Consumer-Farmer Milk Cooperative--Who Is Behind Milk Station Closing?, 1955 Feb. 28 (Box 19)
  - Consumers Cooperation--The Co-operative Builder, 1937 Feb. 6 (Box 19)
  - Consumers Cooperative Association--Neighborhood Council News, 1940 Dec. (Box 16)
  - Consumers Cooperative Association--The Cooperative Consumer, 1941, 1958 (Box 19)
  - Consumers Cooperative Services--Co-Op Cafeterias "Table Talk", 1940-1941 (Box 16)
  - Consumers Mail-Order Cooperative--Consumer's Aid, 1939 (Box 16)
  - Cooperative Federation of New Jersey--New Jersey Federation Flashes, 1941 June (Box 16)
  - Cooperative Grocery Stores--Co-op Homemaker, 1941 (Box 19)
  - Cooperative Homes Society--CHS Housing Bulletin, 1936 Sept. (Box 17)
  - Cooperative League News Service, 1939-1959 (Box 17)
  - Cooperative Publishers (Canada)--The Cowbell, 1937 Nov. (Box 17)
  - Cooperative Union of Canada--The Canadian Co-operator, 1934 June (Box 17)
  - Co-ordinating Council of 213 Co-operatives--213 Co-op News, 1955 Oct. (Box 19)
  - Crowley's Producer's Bulletin, 1938-1939 (Box 17)
  - Daily Compass, 1949 May 16 (Box 19)
  - Daily Record, 1944 (Box 17)
  - Dairy Farmers Digest, 1943-1948; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Dairy Farmers Digest and Poultry News, 1941-1943 (Box 17)
  - Dairy Farmers Information Council pamphlets, 1939-1940 (Box 17)
  - Dairy Farmers of America--The Defender, 1959-1961 (Box 17)
  - Dairy Farmers Union--Poster "Farmer Get Ready" protest and demands, undated (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Dairy Farmers Union--The Dairy Farmer, 1938-1939 (Box 19)
  - Dairy Farmers Union--The Union Farmer, 1940-1942 and undated; 3 folders (Box 19)
  - Dairy Farmers Union Bulletin, 1937 (Box 17)
  - Dairy Industry Newsletter, 1963-1966 (Box 17)
  - Dairymen's League Cooperative Association--Dairymen's League News, 1937-1938 (Box 19)
  - Deepdale Gardens Community Council--Deepdale Gardens Reporter, 1955 May (Box 19)
  - Eastern Cooperative Wholesale Newsletter, 1937 Jan. 23 (Box 17)
  - Farm Research--Facts for Farmers, 1945-1955 (Box 17)
  - Farmers Defender, 1942-1947; 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Farmers Defender--Northeastern Union Farmer, 1948-1949 (Box 17)
  - Farmers Educational and Cooperative Union--Referendum broadside, 1946 (Box 19)
  - Farmers Educational and Cooperative Union of America, Eastern Division--Eastern Union Farmer, undated (Box 19)
  - Farmers Union Herald, 1957 Dec. 23 (Box 19)
  - Federal Works Agency--Consumer Wise, 1941-1942 (Box 17)
  - Fortune Magazine--Let 'Em Drink Grade A, 1939 Nov. (Box 19)
    Includes response by Edward Fisher Brown (Milk Research Council), "Let 'Em Eat Fortune"
  - Fresh Milk from Cans, undated (Box 19)
  - Greenbelt Consumer Services--Co-op Consumer, 1967-1974 (Box 19)
  - Greenbelt Consumer Services--Co-op Newsletter, 1959-1960 (Box 17)
  - Greenbelt Consumer Services--Co-op Newsletter, 1961 July 12 (Box 19)
  - Group Activity Digest, 1941 Feb. (Box 17)
  - Group Education Service--Leaders' Aid Bulletin, 1941 Feb. (Box 17)
  - Hamilton Grange Co-operator, 1936 Oct. (Box 17)
  - Hillside Producers Cooperative--The Hillside Producer, 1941-1943 (Box 17)
  - In Fact, 1941, 1949 (Box 17)
  - Independent Butcher, 1938 Aug. 23 (Box 19)
  - International Federation of Agricultural Producers--IAFP News, 1953 (Box 17)
  - J. C. Rich--How to Milk a Dry Cow (from The Hat Worker), 1949 (Box 19)
  - James Boyle--Milk: A Public Utility? (in Barron's), 1933 Sept. 4 (Box 19)
  - Knickerbocker Village Co-op--K.V. Consumer, 1938 Dec. (Box 19)
  - Knickerbocker Village Tenants Association--Knickerbocker News, 1939 Mar. 24 (Box 19)
  - Manhattan Consumers Cooperative Federation--Manhattan Cooperator, 1938 Jan. (Box 17)
  - Metropolitan Cooperative Milk Producers--Metropolitan Milk Producers News, 1953 Feb. (Box 17)
  - Metropolitan Cooperative Milk Producers Bargaining Agency--Metropolitan Milk Producers News, 1941 May 2 (Box 19)
  - Meyer Parodneck--Peddlers of Poison (in The Fight), 1939 Apr. (Box 19)
  - Milk Industry Foundation--Milk Industry for Victory, 1944-1946 (Box 17)
  - Milk Industry Foundation--Milk Industry News, 1946-1949 (Box 17)
  - National Cooperatives--Co-op Magazine, 1947 (Box 17)
  - National Farmers Union--Farmers Union in Washington, 1952 (Box 17)
  - National Farmers Union--Proposals broadside, 1946 (Box 19)
  - National Issues, 1939 Mar. (Box 17)
  - National Public Housing Conference--Public Housing, 1943-1945 (Box 17)
  - National Public Housing Conference--Public Housing Progress, 1938-1940 (Box 17)
  - Nearby Egg and Poultry Producers Cooperative Association--The Nearby Cackler, 1944 (Box 17)
  - New England Cooperative News, 1934 (Box 19)
  - New York Adult Education Council Bulletin, 1939 (Box 17)
  - New York State Farm Council Communist Political Association--Farm Front, 1944-1948 (Box 17)
  - Northridge Community Association--Northridge News, 1955 May (Box 17)
  - Pakinghouse Workers of America--The Meat of It, 1947 (Box 17)
  - Parkchester Co-operator, 1943 Jan. (Box 17)
  - Pennsylvania Farm Bureau Federation--Pennsylvania Co-op Review, 1940 Feb. (Box 17)
  - Progressive Women's Council--Voice of the Council, 1937 Nov. (Box 19)
  - Propaganda Analysis, 1938-1939 (Box 17)
  - Red Hook Housing Project--Project Progress, 1940 Feb. (Box 19)
  - Sheffield Producers Cooperative Association--The Sheffield Producer, 1937 Dec. (Box 19)
  - St. Clair-Macomb Consumers Cooperative--Co-op Newsletter, 1960 (Box 17)
  - Soviet Russia Today, 1937 June (Box 17)
  - Sunnyside Consumers News Bulletin, 1933 (Box 17)
  - Sunnyside Gardens Community Association--The Sunnyside News, 1935 July (Box 17)
  - The Nation, 1934 Feb.-Mar. (Box 17)
  - The New Republic, 1935 Mar. 20 (Box 17)
  - U.S. Week, 1941 Nov. 1 (Box 17)
  - United Housing Foundation--The Cooperator, 1967-1969 (Box 19)
  - United Neighborhood Houses of New York--United Neighborhood Houses News, 1957, 1977 (Box 19)
  - Village Cooperators--The Co-operative Village, undated (Box 17)
  - Vox Co-op, 1939 Aug. 1 (Box 17)
  - Weekly Legislative News-Letter, 1939 Mar. 29 (Box 17)
  - Welfare Council of New York City--Better Times, 1939 Feb. 17 (Box 17)
  - West Side Retail Food Merchants Association--The West Side Bulletin, 1942 (Box 17)
  - Woodside Co-op News, 1938 Apr. (Box 17)